mannpill.com 2009-03-26

# Privacy Statement | mannpill.com

**Mannpill.com Privacy Statement**  
What follows is the Privacy Statement for all Bucking Bronco publications and mannpill.com domains.  
Please read this statement regarding our blogs.  
Email Addresses  
You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites.  
We hate spam, popups, adware, spyware and all those really irritating and invasive techniques that are all too common. We will NEVER use such deceptive techniques in our website(s) or our software.

  Ownership of Information

  Mannpill Pubiications is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.  
Comments/Message Boards  
Mannpill websites contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce "comment spam." These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.  
Cookies  
Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.  
Third Party Cookies  
Many of our advertisers use cookies in order to determine the number of times you have seen an advertisement. This is done to limit the number times you are shown the same advertisement.  
Traffic Reports  
Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.  
Business Transitions  
If Mannpill is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.  
Links  
Mannpill websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site's privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Mannpill.  
Notification of Changes  
When Mannpill makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.  
Contact Information  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
